const Qdata = {
questions: [
  {
    question:
      "Which player scored the fastest hat-trick in the Premier League?",
    answerOptions: [
      "Jamie Vardy",
      "Sadio Mane",
      "Harry Kane",
      "Marcus Rashford",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Sadio Mane",
  },
  {
    question: "Where was the 1980 European Cup Winnersâ€™ Cup Final held?",
    answerOptions: ["Belgium", "Netherlands", "France", "Russia"],
    correctAnswer: "Belgium",
  },
  {
    question: "Who has scored the most hat tricks in La Liga for Barcelona?",
    answerOptions: [
      "Luis Figo",
      "Zlaton Ibrahimovic",
      "Lionel Messi",
      "Luis Suarez",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Lionel Messi",
  },

  {
    question:
      "Who is the only player to have been a member of the World Cup winning team thrice?",
    answerOptions: ["Diego Maradona", "Pele", "Ronaldo", "Johan Cryuff"],
    correctAnswer: "Pele",
  },

  {
    question: "What year did the Premier League start?",
    answerOptions: [1988, 1989, 1991, 1992],
    correctAnswer: 1992,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player holds the record for the most goals in consecutive Premier League games?",
    answerOptions: [
      "Harry Kane",
      "Sadio Mane",
      "Jamie Vardy",
      "Marcus Rashford",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Jamie Vardy",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Against which team did Wayne Rooney score his Premier League first goal?",
    answerOptions: ["Manchester City", "Liverpool", "Chelsea", "Arsenal"],
    correctAnswer: "Arsenal",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who is the only player to have scored a goal and been sent off in the same game?",
    answerOptions: [
      "Son Hiu-Meng",
      "Serge Aurier",
      "Troy Deeney",
      "Pierre-Emerick Aubameyang",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Pierre-Emerick Aubameyang",
  },
  {
    question: "Wembly is a famous football stadium in",
    answerOptions: ["Dallas", "London", "Madrid", "Seoul"],
    correctAnswer: "London",
  },
  {
    question: "Ballon d'Or honour is associated with the game of",
    answerOptions: ["Football", "Cricket", "Basketball", "Hockey"],
    correctAnswer: "Football",
  },
]
} ;

export default Qdata;
